(Leonard:)The thing is, someone's coming over.
Well, no problem. I have three controllers.
The more the merrier.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, it's a date.
I have a date coming over.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Well, you can't blame me
for not jumping to that conclusion.
Why? What's so unusual
about me having a date?
- Well, statistically speaking...
- All right, all right.
(Leonard:)Nevertheless, I have one now...
...and I'd appreciate it if you would,
you know, make yourself scarce.
(Sheldon:)I am a published theoretical physicist
with two doctorates...
...and an IQ which can't be measured
by normal tests.
(Sheldon:)How much scarcer could I be?
(Leonard:)You know what I mean.
Could you just give us a little privacy?
- You want me to leave the apartment?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)You mean just go someplace else
and be...
(Sheldon:)...someplace else?
- Yes.
- But why should I leave?
(Sheldon:)- This is my apartment too.
- I know it is.
(Leonard:)If science ever discovers a second member
of your species...
(Leonard:)...and you two would like some privacy,
I'd be happy to get out of your way.